Hugh Henry

Date of Birth: 19/12/1999

Address: 20 Prince Edward Avenue, McKinnon 3204

Mobile Number: 0413 002 582

E-mail Address: hughcthenry@gmail.com

Education and Training

2012 - 2017 Student at McKinnon Secondary College (Completed)

2018 - Present Studying a Bachelor of Software Engineering (Honours) and Bachelor

of Commerce (majoring in Business Analytics) at Monash University

Previous Working Experience

Feb 2022 - Present Melbourne eResearch Group - Casual Research Assistant

Jan 2022 - Feb 2022 Melbourne eResearch Group - Intern

- Worked as a data analyst writing R scripts to perform spatial analysis as part of an ongoing client project
- Integrated R scripts as plugins into web-based digital twin tool
- Created markdown reports visualising analysis results in order to form spatial models

July 2021 - Dec 2021 Deloitte Digital - Monash IBL Intern

- Worked as a junior front-end web developer on the first release of an ongoing client project
- Built reusable components and dynamic pages and page flows using React JS,
 Next.js and SCSS
- Worked in a large development team, regularly reviewing and testing other developers' work
- Participated in daily standups, high-level project meetings, sprint planning and sprint retrospectives

July 2020 - Aug 2020 Melbourne eResearch Group - Intern

- Worked independently to complete a proof-of-project iOS application to be used to collect data through surveys from people diagnosed with Polycystic Ovarian Syndrome
- Linked the application with a local database and implemented RSA security to protect the privacy of respondents

Jan 2018 – June 2021 Officeworks Mentone - Casual Team Member

- Worked mainly in a sales and customer service role
- Provided customers with creative solutions for their technological problems, including: helping them with mobile phones, computers, networking products, cables and iOS devices
- Worked closely with a large and diverse team, constantly communicating with one another in person and via radio headsets

Oct 2016 - Mar 2020 Squash (sports) Coach at The Bentleigh Club - Volunteer

- Coaching players ranging from young children to adults (ages 4 60)
- Co-manager of The Bentleigh Club Squash Group Facebook page
- Member of The Bentleigh Club Squash committee

Personal Statement

I am currently undertaking a Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering (Honours) and a Bachelor's degree in Commerce (majoring in Business Analytics) at Monash University. I enjoy physical activities such as walking my dogs, sports, yoga and bouldering. I spend a lot of time on personal projects including building mobile games, and developing web applications, with the occasional backend application to support them.

Referees

Prof. Richard Sinnott

Director - eResearch, University of Melbourne

Mob: 0435 964 844

E: rsinnott@unimelb.edu.au

Alessandro Cesana

Senior Consultant - Frontend, Deloitte Digital

Mob: 0420 660 236

E: acesana@deloitte.com.au

Adam Piotrowski

Store Leadership Team, Officeworks Mentone

Mob: 0407 007 128

E: adapio01@live.com.au